<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Empowering the Voter</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="clinton_description">An American politician. She is a candidate for the Democratic nomination for President of the United States in the 2016 election. She was the 67th United States Secretary of State from 2009 to 2013. From 2001 to 2009, Clinton served as a United States Senator from New York. She is the wife of the 42nd President of the United States Bill Clinton, and was First Lady of the United States during his tenure from 1993 to 2001.</string>
    <string name="sanders_description">An American politician and the junior United States senator from Vermont. He is a candidate for the Democratic nomination for President of the United States in the 2016 election. A member of the Democratic Party since 2015,[2] Sanders had been the longest-serving independent in U.S. congressional history, though his caucusing with the Democrats entitled him to committee assignments and at times gave Democrats a majority. Sanders became the ranking minority member on the Senate Budget Committee in January 2015; he had previously served for two years as chair of the Senate Veterans\' Affairs Committee.</string>
    <string name="cruz_description">An American politician and the junior United States Senator from Texas. He is a candidate for the Republican nomination for President of the United States in the 2016 election.</string>
    <string name="trump_description">An American businessman, politician, television personality, author, and candidate for the Republican nomination for President of the United States in the 2016 election. Trump is the Chairman and President of The Trump Organization, as well as the founder of the gaming and hotel enterprise, Trump Entertainment Resorts, now owned by Carl Icahn.</string>
    <string name="polling_location">ELLICOTT MILLS MD SCHOOL - CAFETERIA \n 4445 Montgomery RD, Ellicott City, 21043</string>
    <string name="what_information">In U.S. politics, general elections are elections held at any level (e.g. city, county, congressional district, state) that involve competition between at least two parties. General elections occur every two to six years (depending on the positions being filled with most positions good for four years) and include the presidential election, but unlike parliamentary systems the term can also refer to special elections that fill out positions prematurely vacated by the previous office holder (e.g. through death, resignation, etc.). Some parallels can be drawn between the general election in parliamentary systems and the biennial elections determining all House seats, although there is no analogue to \"calling early elections\" in the U.S., and the members of the elected U.S. Senate face elections of only one-third at a time at two-year intervals including during a general election. Unlike parliamentary systems where the term is distinguished from by-elections, a general election in the US is used in reference to and distinguished from primaries or caucuses, which are intra-party elections meant to select a party\'s candidate for a particular race.</string>
</resources>
